{
    "subject": "resource/Martinetes",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Spanish_dances",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Martinetes is Spanish dances.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9108594059944153,
            "question": "What is the significance of Martinetes dances in Spanish culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.701585054397583,
            "question": "What regions in Spain are Martinetes commonly performed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6809453368186951,
            "question": "Can you describe the style of Martinetes dances?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6259327530860901,
            "question": "What country are Martinetes dances from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6099406480789185,
            "question": "Are there any specific musical instruments associated with Martinetes dances?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5806698203086853,
            "question": "What are Martinetes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5447518825531006,
            "question": "Are there any historical events or traditions connected to Martinetes dances?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44813477993011475,
            "question": "Are there any famous performers or troupes known for their Martinetes dance skills?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4133484661579132,
            "question": "How have Martinetes dances evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.224784716963768,
            "question": "What type of cultural expression are Martinetes?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Martinetes is Spanish dances.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7621_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How have Martinetes dances evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7621_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous performers or troupes known for their Martinetes dance skills?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7621_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical events or traditions connected to Martinetes dances?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7621_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7621_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about different styles and aspects of flamenco, including specific mentions of \"martinetes\" as a form within the broader context of Spanish dance. Therefore, the statement that the subject of Martinetes is Spanish dances is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}